pureflix.com 2017-06-10

# Pure Flix - PureFlix Privacy and Netiquette Policies

On behalf of Pure Flix, we are thrilled that you have chosen to take the time to engage in and share your knowledge and life experience with our online community.  We encourage our community to be respectful and professional at ALL times, bearing in mind that your words can either lead a person towards Christ or away from Christ. Remember, to many, you are a reflection of the God you serve and the faith you profess. It goes without saying that no foul language, flaming wars, or spamming will be tolerated and an instant deletion of those comment(s) will occur.

Members and visitors to our community are welcome and are invited to abide by the following guidelines:

  1. **Be Respectful of Other's Ideas, Opinions, and Beliefs.** It's fine to disagree with someone, but please respect their right to think differently.
  2. **Avoid Sarcasm.** People can easily misinterpret intent.
  3. **Use Appropriate Language.** Avoid profane, coarse, rough, rude, condescending or insulting language.
  4. **Use Appropriate Salutations.** Refer to others by their internet handles. Absolutely No Name-calling.
  5. **Observe Good Grammar and Spelling.** Please do not shorten the spelling of a word or create an acronym for a phrase unless the word or phrase. Generally accepted IM Shorthand and Chat acronyms are accepted unless an abbreviation or acronym refers to a profane word or phrase. Also, please be aware that the Autocorrect tool can replace words you did not intend to convey.
  6. **Avoid “Flaming”** (Online Screaming). Do not type sentences in all caps. These messages may be subject to deletion at our discretion. 
  7. **No Spamming.** Spamming is defined as sending unwanted advertising messages or the same electronic message over and over. These messages may be subject to deletion at our discretion. 
  8. **Use the Same Etiquette and/or Behavioral Courtesies as You Would in Person.** Treat others as you would want to be treated.

Back to Top

This Privacy Policy explains our policy regarding the collection, use, disclosure and transfer of your information by Pure Flix or its operator, eSalt Media Technologies, LLC ('Pure Flix'). By using, visiting or browsing the Pure Flix service, you accept and agree to our information practices described below. Please note that this Privacy Policy includes embedded hyperlinks that may only be accessed through our website, so if you are reviewing this Privacy Policy through certain Pure Flix ready devices (for example game consoles or Internet enabled televisions), you may need to visit the website to review these hyperlinked terms.

### Collection and Use of Information

We receive and store information, including personal information, about you and your use of our service. This information is gathered in a number of ways, including when you enter it on our website and from interactions with our service. In this Privacy Policy, we use the term “personal information” to mean information that can be used to uniquely identify or contact you. Non-personal information is information that does not permit direct association with you. We may collect, use, transfer and disclose non-personal information for any purpose. You can choose not to provide personal information we may request of you, but, in general, most of the personal information we request is required in order to provide our service and the withholding of such personal information will prevent us from doing so.

When you interact with us, we may ask you to supply us with personal information so that we can provide, enhance and personalize our services and marketing efforts. For similar reasons, we may supplement the personal information you provide with publicly available information about you as well as information from other sources, as permitted by law. We use this personal information for various reasons, including to process your registration, your orders and your payments, and to communicate on these and other topics. For example, we may use your e-mail address or other methods to send newsletters, messages about new Pure Flix features, Pure Flix special offers, promotional announcements, consumer surveys and other correspondence and marketing concerning our service.

We keep track of your interactions with us and collect information related to you and your use of our service, including but not limited to: your online activity, title selections, reviews, ratings, payment history, correspondence, Internet protocol addresses, device and software data (such as type, configuration and unique identifiers), and related activity. We use this information for such purposes as determining your general geographic location, providing localized content, enforcing our terms (such as determining your eligibility for a free trial), providing recommendations on movies & TV shows we think will be enjoyable, personalizing the service and our marketing to better reflect particular interests, tracking your instant-watching hours, determining your Internet service provider, helping us quickly and efficiently respond to inquiries and requests and otherwise analyzing, enhancing, administering or promoting our service offering for you and other users. We may supplement this information with information from other sources, including offline data and your browsing behavior on other sites and interactions with our advertising. We also provide analysis of our users in the aggregate or otherwise in anonymous form to prospective partners, advertisers and other third parties. We may also disclose and otherwise use, on an anonymous basis, movie & TV show ratings, consumption habits, commentary, reviews and other information. For example, we use movie & TV show ratings and consumption behavior to improve our recommendations to you as well as other users.

While using the Pure Flix service, you will have opportunities to post reviews or other information in public forums. Please understand that when you post such information, it is made public and is not subject to this policy. We are not responsible for any third party's use of information you publicly disclose through our service.

From time to time, we may partner with companies whose products we believe will interest our members. In conjunction with these partners, we may send promotional announcements and/or serve web-based advertisements on their behalf, as permitted by law.

It may become possible that you connect one or more social networks (such as Facebook) with your Pure Flix account. If you choose to do so, we will collect and use information from your social networking account(s) and your use of our social features.

Back to Top

### Disclosure of Personal Information

Pure Flix uses or may use other companies, agents or contractors (“Service Providers”) to perform services on our behalf or to assist us with the provision of services to you. For example, we engage Services Providers to provide marketing, communications, infrastructure and IT services, personalize and optimize our service, process credit card transactions, provide customer service, collect debts, analyze and enhance data, including users' interaction with our service, and process consumer surveys. In the course of providing such services, these other companies may have access to your personal information. We do not authorize these companies to use or disclose your personal information except in connection with providing the services we request of them.

We may offer joint promotions or programs that, in order for participation, will require personal information be shared with third parties. For example, we may partner with companies that offer incentives, such as frequent flyer mileage awards, if you sign up or otherwise use our service. In fulfilling these types of promotions, we may share your name and other information in connection with fulfilling the incentive. By participating in such joint promotions or programs, you agree to our sharing of your information. Please note that we do not control the privacy practices of these third party businesses.

Pure Flix also reserves the right to disclose personal information if we reasonably believe that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process, or governmental request, (b) enforce applicable terms of use, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address illegal or suspected illegal activities, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Pure Flix, its users or the public as required or permitted by law. In connection with any reorganization, restructuring, merger or sale, or other transferring of assets we reserve the right to transfer information, including personal information, provided that the receiving party agrees to respect your personal information in a manner that is consistent with our Privacy Policy.

Back to Top

### Other Websites, Platforms and Applications

Now or in the future, the Pure Flix service may be provided through platforms or contain links to sites operated by third parties whose policies regarding the handling of information may differ from ours. For example, you may be able to access the Pure Flix service through platforms such as Roku Streaming Player, iPad or iPhone and a number of other Internet connected devices, such as “smart” televisions. While we endeavor to associate with reputable companies, Pure Flix cannot be responsible for the information handling practices of these other websites and platforms. These websites and platforms have separate and independent privacy statements, notices and terms of use, which we recommend you read carefully. In addition, you may encounter third party applications that interact with the Pure Flix service. To learn more about these, see our Terms of Use.

Back to Top

### Children

You must be 18 years of age or older to subscribe to the Pure Flix service. In certain jurisdictions, the age of majority may be older than 18, in which case, you must satisfy that age in order to become a member. While individuals under the age of 18 may utilize the service, they may do so only with the involvement, supervision, and approval of a parent or legal guardian, and subject to our Terms of Use.

Back to Top

### Right to Access Your Information

We give you access and the ability to update information about your account, including your contact information and your Payment Choice in the "Account" portion of our website. You must be signed in to access "Account." If you have a question regarding our privacy practices, or want to exercise your rights regarding your personal information, please contact us at [support@support.pureflix.com](mailto:support@support.pureflix.com).

Back to Top

### Security

Pure Flix takes information security seriously and uses reasonable administrative, technical, physical and managerial measures to protect your personal information from unauthorized access. For example, we utilize token technology and Secure Sockets Layering (SSL), an industry-standard protocol for certain of your transmissions to us, in order to encrypt certain personal information that you send to us through the registration and sign up process.

Unfortunately, no security system can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Accordingly, we cannot guarantee the security of your information and cannot assume liability for improper access to it. By using our service, including our website and user interfaces, or providing information to us through any means, you agree that we can communicate with you electronically regarding security, privacy, and administrative issues relating to your use of the Pure Flix service.

In order to provide you with ease of access to your account and to help administer the Pure Flix service, Pure Flix implements technology that enables us to recognize you as the account holder and provide you with direct access to your account without requiring you to retype any password or other user identification when you revisit the Pure Flix service. You can choose not to take advantage of this feature on your computer by unchecking the box "Remember me on this computer" when you login on the website and also clearing the passwords and cookies from your computer. To remove access to your Pure Flix account from your devices: (a) visit Your Account (note, deactivation may not occur immediately) or (b) delete your Pure Flix settings from your device (steps vary by device and the option is not available on all devices). You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account access information and for restricting access to your computer or device through which you access your Pure Flix account. Where possible, users of public or shared devices should log out at the completion of each visit and not check the "Remember me on this computer" when logging in to Pure Flix. If you sell or return a computer or Pure Flix ready device, you should log-out and deactivate the device before doing so. If you do not maintain the security of your password or device, or fail to log out or deactivate your device, subsequent users may be able to access your account, including your personal information.

Back to Top

### Transfer of Information

Using the Internet to collect and process information necessarily involves the transmission of data on an international basis. Therefore, by using Pure Flix, you acknowledge and agree to the transfer of your information outside your country of residence to any country (including the United States) where we have facilities or engage third parties (including but not limited to payment processors, cloud service or other IT providers, and other companies that provide services to us). You understand that the countries to which we may transfer information may not have as comprehensive a level of data protection as in your country.

Back to Top

### Changes to This Policy

From time to time, Pure Flix may make changes to this Privacy Policy. Such revisions shall be effective immediately; provided however, for existing members, such revisions shall, unless otherwise stated, be effective 30 days after posting.

Back to Top

### Contacting Us

eSalt Media Technologies, LLC, through PureFlix.com and its Pure Flix service, is providing the service to you and is the data controller (where applicable).

If you have questions concerning your account, please contact Customer Service. If you have questions concerning this Privacy Policy, including the treatment of your personal information and/or our use of cookies and other technologies, please contact us via email at [support@support.pureflix.com](mailto:support@support.pureflix.com), or at the following:

    eSalt Media Technologies, LLC  
    18940 N. Pima Road, Suite 110  
    Scottsdale, AZ 85255, U.S.  
    Attention: General Counsel.

Back to Top

Last Updated: May 06, 2016
